A Guide to the Gravely Family Papers, 1753-1988
Library of Virginia
- Series IX: Business records
  - Subseries 5: Invoices and bills
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1889 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1890 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1890 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1891 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1892 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1892 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1893 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1894 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1894 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1894 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1894 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1894 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1896 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1896 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1897 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1897 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895-1899 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895-1899 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895-1899 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895-1899 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895-1899 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895-1899 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895-1899 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895-1899 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895-1899 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1895-1899 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1898-1899 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1901 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1900-1904 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1905 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1905-1909 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1905-1909 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1905-1909 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1905-1909 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, nd (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, nd (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, nd (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, nd (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, nd (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, nd (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, nd (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 6: Incoming letters
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1851 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1852 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1853 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1854 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1857 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1858 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1859 (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1860 (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1862 (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1865 (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1866 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1867 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1868 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1871 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1878 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1879 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1890 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1891 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1892 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1893 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1898 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1901 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1901 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1903 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1904 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1904 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons 1905 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 7: Miscellaneous
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1820-1839 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1840 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1841 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1842 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1843 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1843-1844 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1844 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1845 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1846 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1847 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1848 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1849 (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1850 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1851 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1852 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1853 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1854 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, 1857 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Peyton and Willis Gravely, nd (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, Peyton 1836-1864 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, Peyton 1855 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Gravely, Peyton 1856 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Gravely, Peyton 1858 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Gravely, Peyton 1860 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Gravely, Peyton 1861 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Gravely, Peyton 1862 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Gravely, Peyton 1863 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Gravely, Peyton 1865 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Burnett and Gravely, 1867 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - D.H. Spencer and Sons Inc., 1904-1905 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - D.H. Spencer and Sons, Inc., 1905-1908 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - David Farley and Co., 1866 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Dyer and Company, 1867 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Gravely and Burch, nd (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Gravely Furniture Co., 1979-1985 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Gravely Novelty Furniture Co., 1926-1929 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Gravely, Sowers, and Co., 1867 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Henry County Telephone Company, 1904-1905 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Henry County Telephone Company, 1904-1914 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - J.T. Slaydon and Company, 1870-1872 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Johnston, Clarke and Company, 1860-1861 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Liberty Cigar Manufacturing Co., 1890 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - McGreenery and Manning, 1905 (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - P.F. Gravely Tobacco Co., 1902 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Riverside Cotton Mills, 1893 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Riverside Cotton Mills, 1895-1913 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - T.S. Holland and Company, 1867-1869 (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Weber and Erskine, 1905 (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Subseries 8: Government
    - Henry County Sheriff, 1866-1867 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Martinsville School District, 1876-1878 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 9: Ephemera
    - Tobacco agreement, tobacco tags (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Tobacco tags (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Business cards, tobacco labels, postcards, 1904-1912 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Smithdeal Business College flyer, 1902 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Business cards (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1880-1931 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1886-1926 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1887-1896 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1896 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1899-1905 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1899-1905 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1899-1928 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1900 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1902-1915 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1905 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1912-1913 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1912 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1912-1913 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides, 1913 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Printed advertisements, circulars, broadsides (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Gravely, B.F., Subject files, 1868-1869 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, B.F., Legal documents, 1879 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, B.F., Business records, Correspondence, 1870 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely Tobacco, Metal sign (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Broadsides and missionary maps (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Plats and surveys, 1935-1965 (Box Mapcase, Folder Mapcase (folder marked 1284))
    - Woodson, Eliza Smith Reamey, Files (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Pannill, Amy, Scrapbook (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Salem-Roanoke Valley Historical Society Edition, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 10: Business covers
    - Businesses, A (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Businesses, B-Baugh (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Businesses, Baughman-Butterworth (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Businesses, C-Century (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Businesses, Charles-Cussons (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Businesses, D (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Businesses, E (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Businesses, F (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Businesses, Fa-Fr (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Businesses, G (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Businesses, H (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Businesses, Ha-Hy (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Businesses, J.A.-J.R. (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Businesses, J.S.-Je (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Businesses, Jno.-Jo (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Businesses, K (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Businesses, L (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Businesses, M.B.-Mart (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Businesses, Mary-Mu (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Businesses, N (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Businesses, O (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Businesses, P-Q (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Businesses, R.B.-Reg (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Businesses, Rel-Ry (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Businesses, S.C.-Sl (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Businesses, Sm-Southern Stamp (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Businesses, Southern Stove-Sy (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Businesses, T.A.-T.W. (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Businesses, Ta-Tu (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Businesses, U-V (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Businesses, W.A.-W.W. (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Businesses, Wa-Wo (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Businesses, Y-Z (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Educational institutions, A-W (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Series X: Ledgers
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Account Book, nd (Box 92, Volume 1)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Commissary Book, 1868-1869 (Box 92, Volume 2)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Day Book, 1847 (Box 92, Volume 3)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Day Book, 1848 (Box 92, Volume 4)
  - Loose papers from B.F. Gravely & Co., Day Book, 1848 (Post office receipt, 1865, for letters mailed; letter, 1865, from Secretary of the Commonwealth on county reorganization; marriage license, 1866, for Samuel Gravely and Delia Martin, both African American; pages from Jayne's Medical Almanac, 1867; pages from Signs of the Times; and receipts, 1880, for tobacco sales at the Planters' Warehouse in Danville, Virginia.) (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Day Book, 1849 (Box 93, Volume 5)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Day Book, 1854 (Box 93, Volume 6)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Day Book, 1859 (Box 94, Volume 7)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Day Book, 1861-1866 (Box 94, Volume 8)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1856-1864 (Box 95, Volume 9)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1860-1863 (Box 95, Volume 10)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1864-1865 (Box 95, Volume 11)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1866-1869 (Box 95, Volume 12)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1867-1868 (Box 96, Volume 13)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1869-1871 (Box 96, Volume 14)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1872-1873 (Box 96, Volume 15)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1874-1879 (Box 96, Volume 16)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1875-1877 (Box 97, Volume 17)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1877-1878 (Box 97, Volume 18)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1878-1880 (Box 97, Volume 19)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Letter Book, 1878-1882 (Box 97, Volume 20)
  - B.F. Gravely & Co., Memorandum Book, 1847 (Box 98, Volume 21)
  - Tobacco purchases for W.T. Clark (Box 98, Volume 22)
  - Carrington family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Holloway family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Hubbard family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Hubbard family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Keith family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Lewis family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Loving family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Lyne family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Marshall family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - McDowell family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Neil family genealogy 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - O'Hara family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Price family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Reamey family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Rodgers family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Sands family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Smith family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Starling family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Sullivan family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Thomas family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Todd family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Underhill family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Watson family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - Wilcox family genealogy, 1874 (Box 98, Volume 23)
  - B.F. Gravely court memorandum book, 1858 (Box 98, Volume 24)
  - B.F. Gravely account book, 1854-1855 (Box 98, Volume 25)
  - B.F. Gravely store memorandum book, 1856 (Box 98, Volume 26)
  - B.F. Gravely store memorandum book (salt accounts), 1864 (Box 98, Volume 27)
  - B.F. Gravely store memorandum book, 1865-1866 (Box 98, Volume 28)
  - B.F. Gravely tobacco book (includes stud book), 1860-1865 (Box 98, Volume 29)
  - B.F. Gravely tobacco purchases book, 1867 (Box 98, Volume 30)
  - B.F. Gravely Negroes corn account book, 1859-1861 (Box 98, Volume 31)
  - R.P. Gravely private letter book to S. Mullins, 1908-1909 (Box 99, Volume 32)
  - Gravely and Martin account book, nd (Box 99, Volume 33)
  - Henry County Treasurer's office journal (M.A. Thomas guardian account), 1859-1888 (Box 99, Volume 34)
  - 24th Virginia Regiment, CSA, Company H, Henry Guards, Muster roll book, 1899 (Box 99, Volume 35)
  - Justice of the peace order book, 1904-1927 (Box 99, Volume 36)
  - Peyton and Willis Gravely account book (includes employee information and purchases), 1840-1842 (Box 100, Volume 37)
  - Peyton and Willis Gravely daybook, 1831-1839 (Box 100, Volume 38)
  - C.Y. Thomas day book, 1876-1881 (Box 100, Volume 39)
  - Unidentified account book, 1842-1846 (Box 100, Volume 40)
  - Unidentified account book, nd (Box 100, Volume 41)
  - Unidentified account book, nd (Box 100, Volume 42)
  - Hands book, 1868 (Box 100, Volume 43)
  - List of hands, nd (Box 100, Volume 44)
  - Store memorandum book, nd (Box 100, Volume 45)
- Series XI: Postcards
  - Postcards, B.F. Gravely Tobacco Manufacturing-Leatherwood Postmaster, 1878-1904 (Box 101)
  - Postcards, D.H. Spencer and Son, Inc.-W.L. Tuggle, 1878-1951 (Box 102)
- Series XII: Photographs and negatives
  - Subseries 1: Photographs
    - Gravely family (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Gravely family (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Gravely family (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Gravely, Benjamin F. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, Benjamin F., II (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Gravely, Benjamin J. (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Sr. (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Sr. (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Sr. (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. and Richard Pleasants Gravely, III photo album. (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Gravely, Richard Pleasants, Jr. (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Gravely, Nancy (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - Gravely, Nancy (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Gravely, Nancy (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Gravely, Nancy (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - Gravely, Paul (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Gravely, John Thomas (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Lee, Hope Gravely (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Lee, Hope Gravely (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, Ann Hope Thomas (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Gravely, Harold (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, H.C. (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, H.C. (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Gravely, Julia Caroline Thomas (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Leatherwood, Virginia (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Leatherwood, Virginia (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely & Sons Tobacco Factory (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Gravely family (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Gravely family (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, C.Y. (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Thomas, C.Y. (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Thomas, C.Y. (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Thomas, L.S. (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, Katherine (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Martin family (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Gravely, John W. & Hattie M. (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Mullins family (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Mullins family (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Mullins family (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Kearfott, Clarence (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Smith family (Ohio) (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Gravely, Eva Lurita Stone (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Gravely, Eva Lurita Stone (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Fernald, Benjamin Gravely (Canada and New England) (Box 109, Folder 14)